PATRICIA ANDRADES

COMPOSITING ARTIST

<u>andradesdelgado@gmail.com</u>

+34 627 235 460

https://vimeo.com/812551828

password: reelCompAndrades

www.linkedin.com/in/patriciaandrades

ABOUT ME

Compositing Artist in 2D/3D animation and live-action, and 2D Animation Comp Supervisor.

With a career of almost fifteen years in the Audiovisual Industry as a video editor and filmmaker, it was in 2018 when I fully immersed myself in the world of Digital Compositing and FX.

Tenacious, perfectionist and nonconformist in my work, always looking for new challenges to face.

EDUCATION

- Animation Production Course | Lightbox Academy | 2023.
- Master's degree in VFX with Houdini & Nuke | Animum
 Creativity Advanced School | 2017 - 2018.
- Master's degree in Advanced
 3D Production | Animum
 Creativity Advanced School |
 2016.
- Master's degree in Editing and FX for Film and TV | Animum Creativity Advanced School | 2006.
- Degree in Audiovisual
 Communication | Málaga
 University | 2003.

WORK EXPERIENCE

THE LINE ANIMATION STUDIO

Compositing Artist | 2023

Marvel Snap.

MATHEMATIC STUDIO

Compositing Artist | 2023

• Dior Elixir. TV Commercials.

ARCADIA MOTION PICTURES

Compositing Supervisor | 2022 - 2023

• Robot Dreams (2023, Pablo Berger)

CARTOON SALOON

Compositing Artist | 2021 - 2022

• My Father's Dragon (2022, Nora Twomey)

LANDIA

Compositing Artist | 2020

• Doritos | UDLA Ecuador. TV Commercials.

MPC

FX Artist / Compositing Artist | 2019 - 2020

- Cats (2019, Tom Hooper)
- Technicolor Academy

GIANT ANIMATION

Compositing Artist | 2018

• "Sherwood" Animation for Youtube Originals.

ANIMUM CREATIVITY ADVANCED SCHOOL

FX Artist / Compositing Artist | 2018

• Creating VFX Material for the content of the school's Master in VFX with Houdini & Nuke.

TVE | MLK PRODUCCIONES

Colourist / Senior Video Editor | 2016

 Miguel Picazo: un cineasta extramuros (Enrique Iznaola, 2016). Documentary Film.

AWARDS AND SELECTIONS



Senderos (Patricia Andrades / Daniel Martín Novel, 2011). Best Videocreation Award at Festival de Málaga de Cine Español 2011.



Síndrome Arconada (Daniel M. Novel / Patricia Andrades, 2006). Fiction Short Film. Official Short Film Section Málaga. Festival de Málaga de Cine Español 2006.



Tríptico: figuras (Patricia Andrades, 2008). Video Art. Selection Biennial of Young Artists from Europe and the Mediterranean (BJCEM) Skopje, Macedonia 2009.





ART BUSAN

Europa (Patricia Andrades / Daniel Martín Novel, 2013). Official Selection Internacional Video ArtHouse Madrid (IVAHM). Seoul InterNational NewMedia Festival (NEMAF), Korea. 10th International Busan Videoart Festival, Korea.

CONDÉ NAST

Colourist / Senior Video Editor | 2015

• Vanity Fair Commercial.

UNIVERSAL STUDIOS

Director / Senior Video Editor | 2014

• Alejandro Fernández Live. Making Of.

UNIVERSAL STUDIOS

Director / Senior Video Editor | 2013

 Alejandro Sanz, la música no se toca. Live. Making Of.

RTVA

Colourist / Senior Video Editor | 2013 -2017

• Destino Andalucía. RTVA Weekly program.

CEDECOM

Colourist / Senior Video Editor | 2004 -2013

- Andalucía Innova. RTVA weekly program.
- Tesis. RTVA weekly program.
- Tesis en la Internacional. RTVA weekly program.
- Mentes Brillantes. TV Documentary Series.
- Desátate. (Jesús Font, 2009). Feature Film.
 Trailer and promo videos.
- Looking for George. (Luís Maceras, 2007).
 Documentary Feature.

SOFTWARES

Nuke / Toon Boom / Houdini / Resolve / Mocha Pro / ReviewTool / Linux / Shotgrid / Final Cut Pro

/ Avid / Premiere Pro / After Effects / Maya / 3ds Max / PF Track / Photoshop

LANGUAGES

Spanish: Native English: Intermediate